Time is running out.
Breathe is a action, science fiction, mystery film directed by Stefon Bristol.
Air-supply is scarce in the near future, forcing a mother and daughter to fight for
survival when two strangers arrive desperate for an oxygenated haven.
Maya, played by Jennifer Hudson.
Tess, played by Milla Jovovich.
Zora, played by Quvenzhané Wallis.
Darius, played by Common.
Lucas, played by Sam Worthington.
Micah, played by Raúl Castillo.
Breathe is a 2024 American science fiction thriller film directed by Stefon Bristol, written by Doug Simon,
and starring Jennifer Hudson, Milla Jovovich, Quvenzhané Wallis, Common, and Sam Worthington.
The film is set in a world where oxygen levels on Earth have dropped making it
impossible to live on the planet's surface without specialised equipment.
It was released on April 26, 2024.
The film explores themes of air supply, last human,
uninhabitable, oxygen depletion.
The tone is intense and thought_provoking and mind_bending.